Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records UA002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1940 -- 1988; 1943 -- 1982; UA002.001; 13.2 Linear Feet
  - Internal management reports, 1973; UA002.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - International office and Latin-American teaching fellows, 1976 -- 1982; UA002.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - I..??? election of new president, 1965; UA002.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Jackson College, 1970 -- 1977; UA002.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Jackson College, 1960 -- 1968; UA002.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Judaica studies proposal, 1971 -- 1974; UA002.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Learning center, 1974 -- 1976; UA002.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Lectures: faculty & general, 1960 -- 1980; UA002.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Legal audit, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Legal correspondence, 1957 -- 1967; UA002.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - Legal matters, 1973 -- 1981; UA002.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Legislative information, 1969 -- 1976; UA002.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - Liberal arts and Jackson, 1970 -- 1982; UA002.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - Liberal arts and Jackson, 1968 -- 1975; UA002.001.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Libraries, 1982 -- 1984; UA002.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Libraries, 1978 -- 1985; UA002.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Library, 1975; UA002.001.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Library, 1969 -- 1974; UA002.001.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - Library, 1966 -- 1971; UA002.001.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - Library: committees, 1977; UA002.001.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Loans, 1942 -- 1959; UA002.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Majors, 1972; UA002.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Marcos chair, 1977; UA002.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health labs, 1977; UA002.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Matriculation, 1968 -- 1979; UA002.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Mayer, Jean, 1976 -- 1980; UA002.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - McIlroy Fluid Network Computer, 1957 -- 1968; UA002.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Medford, Somerville, 1959 -- 1965; UA002.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Medical school, 1983 -- 1985; UA002.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Medical school, 1983; UA002.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Medical school, 1980 -- 1981; UA002.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Medical school: appendices: educational program, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Medical school: introduction to clinical medicine, 1972; UA002.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Memoranda: general, 1965 -- 1969; UA002.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Microwave communication, 1971 -- 1975; UA002.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Military coordinator, 1969 -- 1974; UA002.001.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Military coordinator, 1960 -- 1968; UA002.001.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Military recruiting, 1968 -- 1972; UA002.001.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Model cities program, 1970; UA002.001.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Model cities program, 1968 -- 1970; UA002.001.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1980; UA002.001.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Motor vehicles, 1960 -- 1965; UA002.001.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Movie, 1953 -- 1965; UA002.001.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Museum School, 1970 -- 1975; UA002.001.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Museum School, 1954 -- 1969; UA002.001.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - National Science Foundation, 1969 -- 1970; UA002.001.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - NDEA Title IV, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.001.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - NDEA Title IV, 1966; UA002.001.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - New England Medical Center, 1965 -- 1969; UA002.001.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - New England Regional Computing Program, 1969 -- 1975; UA002.001.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - NROTC, 1959 -- 1965; UA002.001.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - NSF development proposal, 1968; UA002.001.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - NSF development proposal, 1964 -- 1965; UA002.001.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - NSF development proposal, UA002.001.009.00034 (Box 9)
    Date Not Available
  - Nutrition school, 1977 -- 1985; UA002.001.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Office safety manual, UA002.001.009.00036 (Box 9)
    No Dates Available
  - Organizations, 1972 -- 1984; UA002.001.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Organizations, 1954 -- 1970; UA002.001.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - Orthopedic Associates, 1979 -- 1981; UA002.001.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Parking, 1972 -- 1981; UA002.001.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - Parking, 1965 -- 1969; UA002.001.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Pass-fail options, 1966; UA002.001.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Patents and copyrights, 1978 -- 1980; UA002.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Payment of students, 1979; UA002.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Personnel, 1976 -- 1984; UA002.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - Personnel, 1976 -- 1984; UA002.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Personnel, 1970 -- 1973; UA002.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Personnel, 1970 -- 1973; UA002.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Physical planning, 1968; UA002.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Physical planning, 1953 -- 1967; UA002.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Physical plant, UA002.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Physician's assistant program, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.001.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Placement, 1962 -- 1977; UA002.001.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Planning, 1971; UA002.001.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Planning, 1971; UA002.001.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Promotion and tenure policies, 1962 -- 1968; UA002.001.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Publications, 1970 -- 1984; UA002.001.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Quincy school, 1964 -- 1972; UA002.001.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Radiation hazards, 1971 -- 1978; UA002.001.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Recommendations, 1975 -- 1977; UA002.001.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Registrar, 1973 -- 1983; UA002.001.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - Residences, 1978 -- 1982; UA002.001.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - Residences, 1981; UA002.001.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - Resources, 1972; UA002.001.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - Resources: fundraising, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.001.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - Retired and emeritus, 1971 -- 1981; UA002.001.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - Retired and emeritus, 1971 -- 1979; UA002.001.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - ROTC, 1975 -- 1979; UA002.001.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Sabbatic leave, 1975 -- 1983; UA002.001.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Sackler school, 1979 -- 1981; UA002.001.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - Salary administration, 1980; UA002.001.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Salary administration, UA002.001.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - Salary administration project: status report, 1975; UA002.001.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Salary administration project: status report, 1975; UA002.001.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - Salary studies: senior salary administration committee, 1979; UA002.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - SCAR, 1968; UA002.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Scheduling and registration, 1983 -- 1985; UA002.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Scheduling and registration, 1977 -- 1986; UA002.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Scheduling and registration, 1979 -- 1981; UA002.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Scheduling and registration, 1974 -- 1981; UA002.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Scheduling and registration, 1978 -- 1981; UA002.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Scheduling and registration, 1976 -- 1978; UA002.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Scheduling and registration, 1975 -- 1978; UA002.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Sex discrimination, 1971 -- 1977; UA002.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Sex discrimination, UA002.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Sex discrimination, UA002.001.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Shell assists, 1969 -- 1980; UA002.001.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Shorthand and typing department, 1954 -- 1981; UA002.001.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Sigma Xi, 1957 -- 1978; UA002.001.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Somerville Committee for Racial Understanding, 1968 -- 1970; UA002.001.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Special studies, College of, 1954 -- 1975; UA002.001.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Statistics and special reports, 1954 -- 1971; UA002.001.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Statistics and special reports, 1958 -- 1968; UA002.001.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Student life committee, 1970 -- 1979; UA002.001.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Summer school, 1977 -- 1982; UA002.001.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - TCU, 1980 -- 1985; UA002.001.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - TCU, 1971 -- 1980; UA002.001.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Teacher's oath, 1966 -- 1967; UA002.001.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - Teaching loads, 1951; UA002.001.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1971 -- 1977; UA002.001.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - Traffic commission, 1973 -- 1982; UA002.001.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Tri-partite board, 1968 -- 1979; UA002.001.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Trustee academic affairs committee, 1983; UA002.001.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Trustee ad hoc health science committee, 1978; UA002.001.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - Trustee audit committee, 1986; UA002.001.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - Trustee audit committee, 1986; UA002.001.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - Trustee audit committee, 1986; UA002.001.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - Trustee audit committee, 1985; UA002.001.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - Trustee buildings and grounds committee, 1979 -- 1981; UA002.001.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - Trustee finance committee, 1968 -- 1983; UA002.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Trustee honorary degree committee, 1965 -- 1973; UA002.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Trustee management committee, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Trustee personnel policy committee, 1976 -- 1980; UA002.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1976 -- 1980; UA002.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1972 -- 1977; UA002.001.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - University development, 1980; UA002.001.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - University-wide advisory committee on libraries, 1973 -- 1979; UA002.001.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Women at Tufts, 1976; UA002.001.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - The Women's school, 1976 -- 1978; UA002.001.013.00001 (Box 12)
  - YRO, 1974 -- 1975; UA002.001.013.00002 (Box 12)
  - YRO: calendar arrangements, 1973 -- 1975; UA002.001.013.00003 (Box 12)
  - YRO: calendar arrangements, 1973; UA002.001.013.00004 (Box 12)
- Subject files, 1946 -- 2013; 1983 -- 1994; UA002.002; 33.6 Linear Feet; 1 Web sites
  This series contains subject files from the Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President. The original accession of subject file materials for this collection was arranged in one series titled "Subject Files, 1843-82." This included materials from several provost administrations. When a subsequent accession containing Sol Gittelman records was received in the1980s, a decision was made to create a separate series for each provost. A second subject file series was created at the time. However, subsequent accessions indicated that records of different provosts were not maintained separately in the Office of Provost and significant overlap occurred across administrations. As of summer 2006, archivists decided not to create a new series for each provost. Rather, each new accession will be added to Series 2. This means that each new run of subject files will be arranged alphabetically, and accessions will most likely overlap chronologically reflecting administrative use.
  This series is arranged alphabetically within each accession maintaining original order.
  75 years from the date of creation. 20 years from date of creation.
  - AAUP, 1965; UA002.002.014.00001 (Box 14)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1988 -- 1991; UA002.002.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Accreditation file, 1982; UA002.002.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Admissions, 1983 -- 1985; UA002.002.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Affirmative action plan, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.002.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Affirmative action plan, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.002.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Affirmative action plan, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.002.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Affirmative action plan, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.002.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Affirmative action plan, 1988; UA002.002.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Alumni association, 1965; UA002.002.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Alumni club, 1983; UA002.002.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Alumni office, 1986 -- 1988; UA002.002.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Alumni relations, 1984 -- 1986; UA002.002.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Annual report, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.002.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Annual reports, 1986; UA002.002.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Annual reports, 1987; UA002.002.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Annual reports, 1989; UA002.002.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Appointments, 1985 -- 1987; UA002.002.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Audit plan, 1989; UA002.002.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Ballou curator, 1980; UA002.002.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - BIFAD, 1984; UA002.002.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - BSOT, 1977 -- 1982; UA002.002.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - BSOT, 1977; UA002.002.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - Budget offices, 1988; UA002.002.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Bush, Vannevar: Tufts Medal and National Science Board Award, 1980 -- 1983; UA002.002.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Campus planning, 1979 -- 1984; UA002.002.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - Capital campaigns, 1988; UA002.002.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - CEM, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.002.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - CEM, 1990; UA002.002.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Center for Public Service, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.002.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Center for the Study of Decision Making, 1987; UA002.002.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Committee organizing 10th year celebration, 1986; UA002.002.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - Committees, 1974 -- 1983; UA002.002.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Committees, 1970 -- 1986; UA002.002.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Committees, 1979 -- 1986; UA002.002.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - Coolidge Room refurbishing, 1981 -- 1983; UA002.002.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Communications, 1988 -- 1990; UA002.002.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Communications, 1982 -- 1987; UA002.002.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - Community relations, 1981 -- 1991; UA002.002.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Community relations, 1990; UA002.002.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Community relations, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.002.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Computer services, 1982 -- 1988; UA002.002.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Conference bureau, 1984; UA002.002.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Copyrights and patents, 1974 -- 1984; UA002.002.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Corporation visiting committee, 1978 -- 1984; UA002.002.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Correspondence, 1982 -- 1989; UA002.002.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - CVC, 1975 -- 1987; UA002.002.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - CVC, 1970 -- 1978; UA002.002.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - CVC, 1978 -- 1981; UA002.002.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - CVC, 1980 -- 1986; UA002.002.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Dean of Engineering, 1988; UA002.002.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Dean of students, 1988; UA002.002.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Dean of stuents and coordinator of student affairs, 1965 -- 1976; UA002.002.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Dean of students and coordinator of student affairs, 1959 -- 1965; UA002.002.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Department of personnel, 1984; UA002.002.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Development, 1976 -- 1978; UA002.002.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Development division, 1980; UA002.002.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Development division, 1980; UA002.002.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Dunn, Jack, 1986; UA002.002.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Dunn, Jack, 1987 -- 1991; UA002.002.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Electro-optics technology center, 1988; UA002.002.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Engineering education, 1984; UA002.002.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - European Center, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - European Center, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.002.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - Faculty research, 1971 -- 1986; UA002.002.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - Faculty workload study, 1975; UA002.002.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships, 1986; UA002.002.015.00029 (Box 15)
  - Financial aid, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.002.015.00030 (Box 15)
  - Financial aid, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.002.015.00031 (Box 15)
  - Finance division, 1984; UA002.002.015.00032 (Box 15)
  - Financial aid ombudsman committee, 1981 -- 1984; UA002.002.015.00033 (Box 15)
  - Fine arts, 1985; UA002.002.015.00034 (Box 15)
  - FSLD, 1977 -- 1979; UA002.002.015.00035 (Box 15)
  - General counsel, 1984; UA002.002.015.00036 (Box 15)
  - Government resources, 1984 -- 1990; UA002.002.015.00037 (Box 15)
  - Graduate studies task force, 1987; UA002.002.015.00038 (Box 15)
  - Graduate studies, 1986; UA002.002.015.00039 (Box 15)
  - GSAS, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.002.015.00040 (Box 15)
  - Health science library, 1972 -- 1977; UA002.002.015.00041 (Box 15)
  - Health science library, 1978; UA002.002.015.00042 (Box 15)
  - Health science library, 1978; UA002.002.015.00043 (Box 15)
  - Health science libraries, 1966 -- 1971; UA002.002.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Health service, 1955 -- 1965; UA002.002.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Health service, 1965 -- 1975; UA002.002.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Health service, 1965 -- 1975; UA002.002.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Health service, 1976 -- 1980; UA002.002.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Health service, 1976 -- 1980; UA002.002.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Health services, 1982 -- 1984; UA002.002.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Health services: annual reports, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.002.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - History of Tufts, 1961 -- 1966; UA002.002.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - History of Tufts: affiliation with WGBH, 1946 -- 1968; UA002.002.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - HNRC, 1978 -- 1982; UA002.002.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - HNRC, 1978 -- 1982; UA002.002.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - HNRC, 1978 -- 1982; UA002.002.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - HNRC, 1978 -- 1982; UA002.002.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - HSL, 1985; UA002.002.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Hillel, 1985; UA002.002.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Immunology, 1972; UA002.002.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Information science, 1975; UA002.002.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Information technology, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.002.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Innovative education, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.002.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Insurance, 1971 -- 1978; UA002.002.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Internal audit department, 1984; UA002.002.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - International center, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - International programs, 1989; UA002.002.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - International relations, 1987; UA002.002.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - International relations, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.016.00026 (Box 16)
  - ISI, 1975; UA002.002.016.00027 (Box 16)
  - ISI, 1975; UA002.002.016.00028 (Box 16)
  - LEAVES, 1969 -- 1975; UA002.002.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Library, 1974; UA002.002.016.00030 (Box 16)
  - Library, 1974; UA002.002.016.00031 (Box 16)
  - Library, 1975; UA002.002.016.00032 (Box 16)
  - Library, 1975; UA002.002.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Library, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.002.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Library, 1978 -- 1980; UA002.002.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Library, 1980 -- 1988; UA002.002.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Library, 1980 -- 1988; UA002.002.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Master plan, 1985; UA002.002.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Medical accreditation, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - Medical accreditation, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Medical-dental library resource project, 1968 -- 1973; UA002.002.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - Medical library resources project, 1967; UA002.002.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Medical library resources project, 1957 -- 1980; UA002.002.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Mellon, 1976; UA002.002.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Merit increase recommendation report, 1981; UA002.002.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Naval ROTC, 1966; UA002.002.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Naval ROTC, 1966; UA002.002.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - NDEA reading institute, 1953 -- 1966; UA002.002.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - NDEA institute, 1965; UA002.002.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - New England Injury Prevention Research Center, 1986; UA002.002.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - New England Medical Center, 1986 -- 1989; UA002.002.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - New York law school, 1980; UA002.002.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - Nutrition inst., 1976 -- 1977; UA002.002.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Nutrition, 1985; UA002.002.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - Office of Government Resources, 1977 -- 1987; UA002.002.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - Office of Government Resources, 1988; UA002.002.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Office of Government Resources, 1980; UA002.002.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Office of Institutional Planning, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.002.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - Opera company, 1969 -- 1972; UA002.002.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Operations division, 1984; UA002.002.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Parking, 1989; UA002.002.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - Patents and copying, 1985; UA002.002.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Personnel, 1964 -- 1984; UA002.002.017.00031 (Box 17)
  - Personnel, 1973 -- 1977; UA002.002.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - Physical education, 1984 -- 1987; UA002.002.017.00033 (Box 17)
  - Physical plant, 1979 -- 1986; UA002.002.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Physical plant, 1974 -- 1980; UA002.002.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - Physical plant, 1986 -- 1988; UA002.002.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - Planning, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.002.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Post-retirement health benefits report, 1992; UA002.002.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - Provost cases: development, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Provost file on Niger project, 1982 -- 1986; UA002.002.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Provost file on Niger project, 1982 -- 1986; UA002.002.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Provost office: grants, 1983; UA002.002.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Provost office: grants, 1983; UA002.002.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - Provost office: annual report, 1985 -- 1991; UA002.002.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - Provost: planning, 1977; UA002.002.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - Provost: planning, 1977; UA002.002.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - Public information, 1961 -- 1968; UA002.002.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - Residences, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.002.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - Residences, 1959 -- 1965; UA002.002.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - Resources: Mr. Sheetz,1964-9, 1964 -- 1969; UA002.002.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - Resources: Mr. Sheetz, 1970 -- 1974; UA002.002.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - Retired and emeritus, 1966; UA002.002.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - Retired and emeritus, 1966; UA002.002.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - W. W. Sayre, 1962 -- 1964; UA002.002.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - School of Nutrition, 1986; UA002.002.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - School of Veterinary, 1983; UA002.002.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 1986; UA002.002.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Scientific affairs committee report, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.002.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Security police, 1961 -- 1965; UA002.002.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - Selective service system policy, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.002.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Shell assist, 1958 -- 1969; UA002.002.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - Subject, 1986 -- 1989; UA002.002.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Subject, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.002.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - Subject, 1989; UA002.002.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - Subject, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.002.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Summer school, 1957 -- 1968; UA002.002.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Summer school, 1972 -- 1978; UA002.002.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - TCU senate, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.002.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - TIAA, 1954 -- 1969; UA002.002.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1983; UA002.002.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Trustees, 1966; UA002.002.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Trustees, 1975 -- 1977; UA002.002.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Trustee audit committee, 1988; UA002.002.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Trustee development committee, 1980; UA002.002.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Trustee development committee, 1980; UA002.002.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Trustee development committee, 1980; UA002.002.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - TUCET, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.002.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Tufts in Boston, 1981; UA002.002.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Tufts in Germany, 1969; UA002.002.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Tufts in Hebrew University, 1982; UA002.002.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Tufts in London, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.002.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Tufts in Mexico, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.002.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Tufts in Paris, 1965; UA002.002.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Tufts in Tubingen, 1972 -- 1979; UA002.002.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - Tufts in Italy, 1963 -- 1965; UA002.002.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1983; UA002.002.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1989; UA002.002.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - TUSVM, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.002.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate admissions, 1988 -- 1992; UA002.002.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate education, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.002.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - University council, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.002.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - University council, 1986 -- 1989; UA002.002.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - University development, 1984; UA002.002.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - University objectives, 1985 -- 1990; UA002.002.019.00030 (Box 19)